profitworks.ca 2018-09-04

# Profitworks Privacy Policy

Details 
     __ Base Website

Thank-you for visiting our website. Please find below our privacy policy for your review. This policy identifies what personal information we collect and how we use that information. Please read this policy before submitting your personal information. By submitting your personal information you are accepting the terms listed below of how we will use your personal information

## Information Collection

We collect and store all information you submit on the website for our future reference. This includes such information as your name, email address, city etc. This information will not be shared with third parties without your approval. There are some locations on this website where there are forms to submit your information to a third party. In those locations it is noted that you are submitting your information to a third party website. What third party companies do with your information is outside of our control and not our responsibility.

## Cookie/Tracking Technology

This website may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the website, and understanding how visitors use the website. Cookies can also help customize the website for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information will not be shared with third parties.

## Use Of Information Collection

The primary use of your personal information will be to contact you related to your free download, product purchase or general inquiry. In addition to this the information we collect will be used for internal marketing analysis and review. Where pertinent we may send you special offers or promotions we may think you are interested in. If at anytime you wish to not receive a particular newsletter or all emails from Profitworks this website allows you to opt out of further mailings for the lists you are a part of. You can do this at any time by going to our [manage subscription page](https://profitworks.ca/component/acymailing/user "Manage Your Subscriptions"). We also provide an unsubscribe option in all marketing emails we send. 

## Commitment To Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy please [Contact Us](https://profitworks.ca/contact-us-55.html "Contact Us").
